# **Evy Haan**

Content Designer | Curious Dabbler

Adept adaptor and wide-eyed observer. I enjoy devising frictionless flows for everyday people doing everyday things. I value knowledge-sharing, empathy, and objectivity. I want to design digital experiences that are more human(-friendly).

253.324.0736 evy-content.design evy.haan@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/evyhaan Seattle, WA, USA

## **Relevant Projects**

# UX Writer, Student | Handshake App

lan 2022

- Developed content strategy deliverables for a fictional business management app
- Conducted a competitor analysis to understand user needs, current industry approach, and determine niche-fit
- Conceived the product persona, giving it voice, tone, and core principles
- Crafted a style guide to establish initial copy designs and anticipate future challenges
- Iterated on UX copy through the app login, onboarding, project dashboard, and messaging flows
- Established a project board and defined a materials versioning system to support long-term collaboration

# **Professional Experience**

# Software Development Engineer II | Xevo Inc.

Nov 2019 - Jul 2021

- Developed user-interface features for a connected-car infotainment platform
- Collaborated with product managers, designers, engineers, and QA to coordinate product delivery on tight deadlines for customized demos
- Participated in implementation discussions to understand design decisions, triage limitations, and determine development strategy
- Researched device capabilities to weigh solutions for architectural limitations of designs and share findings
- Contributed to a library of reusable UI components to support UX/UI consistency, maintainability, and usability
- Developed automated user-oriented, behavior-driven tests for typical and edge use-cases
- Learned new workflow tools, frameworks, and languages while being engaged in app and library development

## Software Engineer, Contract | Dashbento

Aug 2019 - Dec 2019

- Developed user-facing components and database models for a project management software
- Created user stories to define and prioritize user-oriented criteria
- Participated in code review and collaboration to maintain a clean code base

#### Executive Assistant | Pioneer Human Services

Feb 2018 - Oct 2018

- Organized materials and schedule for the VP of Advocacy & Philanthropy for seamless daily flow
- Worked with cross-division senior leaders to coordinate objectives with competing deadlines
- Pre-reviewed grant applications, press releases, report slide decks, and department documents to ease the final approval process
- Processed membership renewals to maintain the organization's community presence
- Maintained a report summary of grant and contract application progress

## Administrative Assistant | Pioneer Human Services

Mar 2016 - Feb 2018

- Liaised on-the-ground details for the International Community Corrections Association annual conference
- Managed corporate files including 65+ vehicles, 250 + drivers, and archives for 20+ programs providing treatment, rehabilitation, housing, enterprise, and workforce development services
- Implemented employee recognition rewards program for 1000+ state-wide employees
- Assisted admin team in supporting clients exiting incarceration, company employees, and senior leadership
- Proposed policy changes and updated procedure documents based on unique program needs and local, state, and federal guidelines

# Supported Employment Specialist | Trillium Employment Services

Nov 2014 - Oct 2015

- Coached a caseload of 8-12 clients with diverse disabilities in job search preparation and ongoing job skills
- Created and conducted vocational skill & interest assessments to observe themes in workstyle strengths, preferences, and motivations
- Discussed supported employment with community businesses to encourage inclusive workplaces
- Communicated goals and progress reports with clients, supervisors, guardians, and case managers for coordinated support

# Volunteer Highlights

# Interview Practice Night Host | Puget Sound Programming Python (PuPPy)

Sep 2019 - Feb 2020

- Welcomed attendees, introduced PuPPy, and presented event structure, goals, and expectations
- Prepared practice materials and space setup/cleanup, acted as time-keeper for interview sessions, observed and gave feedback to practice groups
- Answered questions about interview practice, other PuPPy events, networking, resources, and supported attendees in reviewing additional job application materials

## Membership Co-Chair Boardmember | PNW Society for Public Health Education

Feb 2018 - Aug 2018

- Sent a welcome email to new members to establish connection and community
- Organized an event on Trauma-Informed Care for members seeking continuing education credits toward maintaining professional certifications

## Grantwriter | New Way Ministries

lan 2014 - Oct 2014

- Secured a \$5000 grant (request for \$3000) toward operating expenses of a women's shelter
- Secured a \$1000 grant toward purchasing a new playground structure

## **Tools & Technologies**

Figma, Cloudinary, Jira, Confluence, Miro, G Suite, Git, Android Studio, VSCode, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JSON

#### Education

Certificate in Fundamentals of UX Writing | UX Content Collective, Remote

2022

Advanced Software Development Certificate | Code Fellows, Seattle, WA

2019

Community Health Education, BS | Western Washington University, Bellingham, WA

2013

Minors: Psychology, Communication